Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files, 167548
  - Dean's Council Dean's Lecture Series, 1968-; 167588 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Deans Council Minutes/Agenda's, 1974-1976; 167587 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, Agenda, Notes, 1975-, undated; 167586 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Discretionary Fund 8-8570-416, 1971-1973; 167585 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Dean of Faculty of A & S, 1973-; 167584 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Dean's List, 1967-1970; 167583 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Deanship, WSC, 1968-; 167582 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Dean, Vera, 1961-1967; 167581 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Debate Team, 1963-1966; 167580 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Degree Candidates; Graduates, 1971-1972; 167579 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Degree Program, Three -year, 1971-1972; 167578 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Discipline, 1968-1976; 167577 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Discipline Policy, 1947-1970; 167576 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Discipline Policy, 1968-1969; 167575 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Senate: Discipline Procedures, 1968-1969; 167574 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Disciplinary Panel Hearings, 1974; 167573 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Student Disciplinary Proceedings at NYU (adopted by Senate 11/12/1970), 167572 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Disruption, 1968-1970; 167571 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Student Disorders: Analysis, 1969; 167570 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Distinctive Roll, 1963; 167569 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Doctoral Council, New York State, 1974-1975; 167568 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Distiguished Professorships, 1964-1968; 167567 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Dow Chemical Corporation, 1968; 167566 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Draft, 1973; 167565 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Draft Classification, 1967-1968; 167564 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Dress, 1964; 167563 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Dramatic Literature, 1967-1975; 167562 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Dreyfuss, Camille & Henry Foundation Proposal, 1975; 167561 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Drugs, 1971; 167560 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Dual Major, 1967; 167559 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Duplication of Courses, 1969-1974; 167558 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - E miscellaneous, 1964-1969; 167557 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Education Policy Committee Reports, 1963-1967; 167556 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Education Professions Development Act, 1965-1970; 167555 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Early Decisions at NYU Medical, 1973; 167554 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Economics, 1966-1975; 167553 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Enviromental Science and Engineering Group, 1969; 167552 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Econmics Brochure, 1975; 167551 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Evening College of Arts & Science, 1966-1968; 167550 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Evening Division, 1962-1965; 167549 (Box 53, Folder 52)